https://pokerrunsamerica.com/privacy/

Boating News
The Cat is Back: New Company formed to build Pantera Powerboats
Reviews
AllBoat TestsCatamaranCenter ConsoleEngine ReviewsTech ReviewsVee Bottom Test
Privacy Policy
Taylor Publishing Group is committed to keeping personal information accurate, confidential, secure, and private. Our Corporate Privacy Code builds on this commitment.
This Corporate Privacy Code provides guidelines that Taylor Publishing Group uses to protect the privacy of personal information, no matter how the information is collected or stored. In addition to our Corporate Code, each division of Taylor Publishing Group has developed and maintains its own privacy policy.
The Corporate Privacy Code consists of ten principles. Each corporate division’s privacy policy follows the ten principles as they may apply to their business. In addition, each division may:
define how it subscribes to each principle
modify details to provide specific examples
include additional measures for the protection of personal information.
Taylor Publishing Group Privacy Code is based on the Canadian Standards Association (CSA) Model Code for the Protection of Personal Information (CAN/CSA-Q830-96). As part of our mandate, Taylor Publishing Group will continue to review its Privacy Code every two years to ensure it is relevant and up to date.
THE TEN PRIVACY PRINCIPLES
Principle 1 Accountability
Principle 2 Identifying Purposes for which Personal Information is Collected
Principle 3 Getting Consent
Principle 4 Limits on Collecting Personal Information
Principle 5 Limits for Using, Disclosing, and Keeping Personal Information
Principle 6 Keeping Personal Information Accurate
Principle 7 Safeguarding Personal Information
Principle 8 Making Information About Policies and Procedures Available
Principle 9 Individual Access to Personal Information
Principle 10 Handling Complaints and Questions
1. Accountability
Taylor Publishing Group is accountable for all information in its control. Mr. William Taylor, the Publisher, is the designated Chief Privacy Officer. The Chief Privacy Officer is accountable for Taylor Publishing Group compliance with the ten privacy principles.
Taylor Publishing Group recognizes that it is responsible for personal information in its possession or custody, including information that has been transferred to a third party for processing.
Taylor Publishing Group abides by the provisions of the federal law and assumes responsibility for doing so.
2. Identifying Purposes
Taylor Publishing Group makes all reasonable efforts to ensure that we specify the nature of the intended use of the data at or before the time the information is collected.
3. Consent
Taylor Publishing Group makes all reasonable efforts to ensure that organizations providing personal information to us or to our clients have obtained consent from the consumer before disclosing this personal information.
Taylor Publishing Group ensures that all list and other media owners have provided their consumers with a meaningful opportunity to decline to have their name or other information used for any further marketing purposes by a third party.
4. Limiting Collection
Taylor Publishing Group makes all reasonable efforts to ensure that we limit the collection of the personal information on our lists to that which is necessary for the intended use as identified under Principle 2, Identifying Purposes.
5. Limiting Use, Disclosure, and Retention
Taylor Publishing Group agrees to keep personal information only as long as necessary for the identified purposes. Formal guidelines and procedures to ensure the safe destruction or disposal of personal information no longer required are established and have been implemented.
6. Accuracy
Taylor Publishing Group keeps personal information on consumers as up to date as possible for the defined need.
7. Safeguards
Taylor Publishing Group takes responsibility for the protection of list data. This includes, but is not limited to, restricting physical access to data, organizational restrictions through security clearances on a “need-to-know” basis, and technological measures such as passwords and encryption. Care is also used in the disposal or destruction of personal information so as to prevent unauthorized parties from gaining access to this information.
8. Openness
Taylor Publishing Group is open and forthcoming about the policies and procedures it uses to manage personal information. Consumers have ready access to information about these policies and procedures. Taylor Publishing Group makes every effort to ensure that the consumer easily understands personal information handling practices and procedures.
The Chief Privacy Officer, accountable for Taylor Publishing Group policies and practices relating to privacy, and to whom complaints or inquiries can be forwarded is as follows:
Mr. William Taylor
Taylor Publishing Group
268-44 Crawford Crescent
Campbellville, Ontario
L0P 1B0
A copy of any information that explains Taylor Publishing Group privacy policies, standards, and practices is available upon written request to Mr. Taylor at the above address and in addition, it is posted on our website under Privacy at www.powerboating.com and on our other related websites.
9. Individual Access
Taylor Publishing Group will work with consumers, list, and other media owners to fulfill the right of the consumer to know of the existence, use, and disclosure of his or her personal information and to provide access to that information.
Taylor Publishing Group will make all reasonable efforts to provide this information to the consumer upon request. The procedure for responding to consumers’ requests for access is available from the Chief Privacy Officer. When a consumer asks, Taylor Publishing Group will make these procedures known to the consumer.
The consumer must recognize that they are required to provide Taylor Publishing Group with sufficient personal information that will allow us to determine whether we do hold a personal information file pertaining to them. The provision of this information shall not be used for any other purpose.
Taylor Publishing Group will respond to a consumer’s request within a reasonable time and at minimal or no cost to the individual. In some cases, where Taylor Publishing Group may have to incur significant and unreasonable costs to fulfill a consumer’s request, the consumer will be advised of this cost. An agreement will be obtained for payment by the consumer prior to Taylor Publishing Group undertaking the work if the consumer is still interested in pursuing his or her request.
If Taylor Publishing Group denies a consumer’s request for access to personal information, we will tell the consumer why. The consumer may then opt to challenge Taylor Publishing Group decision (see Principle 10).
10. Challenging Compliance
Consumers may challenge Taylor Publishing Group compliance with its own privacy code. Taylor Publishing Group has policies and procedures in place to receive, investigate, and respond to consumers’ complaints and inquiries. Information regarding these procedures and the complaint escalation process is available through Taylor Publishing Group Chief Privacy Officer.
Facebook
Instagram
Twitter
Youtube
© Poker Runs America Magazine 2018, Taylor Publishing Group, L0P 1B0. Tel: 905-844-8218.
Copyright 2018 Poker Runs America.
Privacy Policy
and
Terms and Conditions
